###### LIMITED TIME BLACK FRIDAY DEALS - TAKE A PEEK!

DISCOUNT

Save 15% off for life on all dedicated servers using promo code: **15OFFDEDI**

[\[email protected\]](https://www.racknerd.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) [MY ACCOUNT](https://my.racknerd.com/clientarea.php)

Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy.

**About RackNerd**
------------------

We are an IaaS (infrastructure-as-a-service) provider - operating datacenters in multiple locations to provide web hosting solutions for individuals, small business, to enterprises.

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We use this information for no other reason.

We believe that you should know what information we collect from you, as well as how that information is used, disclosed, and protected. We have created this policy statement (the "Policy") to explain our privacy practices and policies.

We will not sell or disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent except as otherwise provided in this Policy or our Terms of Service and Appropriate Use Policy. We may use information about who you are, where and when you browse on the Web, where your wireless device is located, and how you use our network to provide you better service and enrich your user experience when you sign up or use any of our products or services.

RackNerd may make available shorter or machine-readable versions of this Privacy Policy. These additional policies are intended only as summaries of this complete Privacy Policy. This Policy applies to customers who purchase and use our services and products in the United States. Collection, use, disclosure, and protection of personal information may be subject to different regulation outside the United States.

RackNerd will revise and update this Policy as it deems appropriate, including, for example, if our practices change or if changes in the law so require.

**Last Revised 9.18.2019**

* HOSTING SERVICES

* COMPANY

* LEGAL

* CLIENTS

#> connect --social

[\[email protected\]](https://www.racknerd.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) [+1 (888) 881-NERD](tel:+18888816373)

© 2024 RackNerd, All Rights Reserved.
